KIERAN WARWICK

Software Engineer ∼ Rungway

🔇 kieranwarwick.dev 🔽 me@kieranwarwick.dev

Q github.com/kw510

SUMMARY

A product-driven software engineer. Have worked in two startups, where both was leading innovative projects to improve the scale and stabitly of the platform. Main expertise is in event-driven architecture on Go microservices, over gRPC. Considered a generalist programmer.

SKILLS

Languages: Go, TypeScript/JavaScript, SQL, Python, Haskell, Java, C++, C, HTML, CSS, LaTeX

Technologies: GCP, Docker, gRPC, Microservices, Kuber-

netes, Pub/Sub

EXPERIENCE

03/2023 -Present

Software Engineer

Rungway

- Worked on V3 of the platform, which is a whole redesign of the platform. Backend work involved taking 25 complex Java microservices (with shared libraries), and condensing them into 5 simple go microservices.
- Collaborated with the insights team to provide a data dashboard. This was a bespoke piece of work to provide data to certain clients.

GCP / Go / gRPC / Pubsub / RabbitMQ / Java / React

11/2020 -03/2023

Software Engineer

Thirdfort

- Developed and maintained new consistent authorisation system, lead migration of the platform to this new system. This improved GET requests by 47%, to an average of 50ms.
- Built and maintained the billing component, enabling operations to charge clients for exactly what they used on the platform.
- Provided mentoring and coaching support to other members of the team.
- Helped out on devops duties, such as CI/CD to the GCP K8 cluster, as well as managing Pub/Sub message topics and the subscriptions.
- Part of the SRE team to solve production issues, and to fix them as well.
- Worked with product, operations, design, and support, to provide technical knowledge about the system.
 GCP / Go / gRPC / Pubsub / Kafka / Node / React

10/2017 - 06/2018

Taught Academic Representative

The University of Bath

- $\bullet \ \ \text{Gathered and represented students' opinions of the course upon Staff Student Liaison Committees.}$
- Relayed outcomes to both students and the SU, acting as a bridge of communication.
- Negotiated upon the SSLC for higher marks for students who took a calculator exam paper, where a printing error caused no calculators to be provided.

10/2017 -06/2018

Academic Peer Mentor

The University of Bath

· Mentored a small group of first year students, helping them with their studies and adjusting to university.

PROJECTS

Technology

protoc-gen-go-mock (protoc plugin)

Medium / Github

A tool that generates Go language bindings of services in protobuf definition files used mocking gRPC in diffrent frameworks. Built because mocking gRPC frameworks should as easy as generating pb.go files.

Technology

Analysis of Extended-Precision upon GPUs

Github

Uses two floats to estimate a double, with arithmetic operations. Provides a speedup of up to 1.2 on consumer GPUs when compared to a native double.

EDUCATION

2016 - 2020 Master of Computer Science

University of Bath

Graduated with a First Class with Honours

6As, 3Bs, 3Cs - including Maths & English

2013 - 2016 **A-Levels**

Chichester High Schools' Sixth Form

Maths: A*, Further Maths: A, Physics A

2011 - 2013 **GCSE**

Chichester High School for Boys

INTERESTS

Cycling, Coffee, Hackathons, Games, Technology, Bloging

References available on request